MARIA KARLSSON

LEARNING DESIGNER



+46 (0) 705-804566



miachallestad@gmail.com







EXPERIENCES

Learning design E-learning design Training events Project management

Sales & sales support

Product information

Selling points, story, USP:s & FAV:s

Concept development

Company guiding

Administration

Facilitation

Coaching

Customer visit service

CPR

LANGUAGE

Swedish – native language English

ΙT

PowerPoint

Word

Excel

Articulate Storyline, Rise

OTHERS

Driving license Rally license

PROFILE

Motivated, creative and service-minded doer, passionate about changing, improving and developing. To find new solutions and create good conditions to learn and grow. With over 10 years of experience in competence development, at one of Europe's largest suppliers of workplace solutions for offices, schools and care, I have a broad experience bank that includes different types of courses for a variety of professional categories.

WORK HISTORY

LEARNING DESIGNER

Kinnarps AB

- Analyze and identify competence needs, development, administration and implementation of traditional and digital courses.
- Training material design and sales argumentation.
- E-learning & video production.
- Webinar, design and carrying through.
- Customer visits, planning, administration and carrying through.
- Guided factory tours.
- Concept development.

INSIDE SALES BACKOFFICE

Kinnarps AB

- Order registration.
- Replacements.
- Factory outlet, sales and assembly.

OTHERS

- Seller Boutique Såfina in Jönköping.
- Cashier, Ica Maxi Jönköping.
- Warehouse, Falbygdens Ost.
- Cashier, Bilisten gas station in Floby.

2007 - March 2021

Aug. 2003-2007

1999-2003

MARIA KARLSSON

LEARNING DESIGNER



+46 (0) 705-804566





miachallestad@gmail.com







EDUCATION

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Code Institute, Scotland.

- User-centric front-end development.
- Interactive front-end development.
- Data-centric development.
- Fullstack framework development

INFORMATION KNOWLEDGE 10 P

Jönköping University

- Oral presentation and presentation skills.
- Mass media.

MEDIA- AND COMMUNICATION SCIENCE 10 P

Jönköping University

- Intra- och inter-personal communication.
- Organisation and social communication.

SOCIAL SCIENCE PROGRAM

Ållebergsgymnasiet, Falköping

1998-2000

Oct. 2020 - on going

Sept. 2001-Jan 2002

Sept. 2001 - Jan. 2002

COURSES

COACHING

2013

- Business adapted training based on Swedish defense's concept Developing Leadership.
- Basic methodology.
- Coaching conversations.
- Practical training & personal feedback.

FACILITATION

2013

Astrakan Strategisk Utbildning AB

- Meeting management facilitate effective meetings, the facilitator's role, meeting process.
- Techniques, methodology, listening techniques, ice-breakers.

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

2013

Wenells

- Projects, project stakeholders, goal and project arena visualization, project environment, project organization.
- Project planning, risks and possibilities, project carrying through, ending and evaluation.
- Project management.

PRESENTATION SKILLS

2010

Instructor: David Philips

- Structure, spices, body language, golden triangle, PowerPoint, the brain, power posing.

SELLING TECHNIQUE

2008

Trainee Center

- The seller's way to success, rhetoric, sales strategy, sales technique.